For the best experience, please make sure your browser is [up-to-date](https://browser-update.org/update.html) and javascript is enabled.

###### Build Trust and Foster Collaboration on Campus

Join our free webinar for actionable strategies.

Close announcement

* Higher Education
* Other Sectors
* Resources
* About Us

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated on September 16, 2022  

Welcome to the Privacy Policy of Constructive Dialogue Institute, Inc., (the “Company”, “we”, “us” or “our”). We are committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information that we collect, how we obtain it, who is responsible for it when we provide our educational services or through your interaction with us on our U.S.-based website (“Services”), how we use it, who we may disclose it to, and your rights in relation to removing your personal information, or suspending its use. When we use the term “personal information” in this Privacy Policy, it means information that is about you and which identifies you as an individual person.  

If you are a visitor to our Services from outside the USA, please be aware that you may be transferring your personal data to the USA, and that the laws in the USA governing privacy may be different than those in your home country.

**1\. Collection of Personal Information.**

Some of the personal information collected by us is required for registration or business interaction purposes, and other information is voluntarily given by you when you interact with our Services. The type of personal information that the Company may collect and store may include without limitation the following:

* Your full name
* Your physical address
* Your telephone number
* Your email address
* Your areas of Services interest or Services preferences
* The progress and results of your use of the Services
* Any other information relating to you that you may provide to us

We collect information when you provide it to us, such as when you “contact us” by email or otherwise, or when you register to do business with us. We may also automatically collect certain information through means such as cookies or web beacons when you use our Services, such as information collected from your browser or device (e.g., the IP addresses and domain names of visitors, type or name of browser, page view history and other usage information about your use of our Services). We may collect this information for website administration and statistical purposes in order to help us improve our Services and create a better experience for all our customers. If you choose to provide the data to us, you are granting consent for us to use of this data for the purpose of the Services.

**2\. **USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION****

We may collect personal information for the purposes set forth below:

* To register individuals for Services use or use of the Services
* To provide our Services to you and our other customers
* To administer and improve the Services
* To facilitate the Company’s research activities
* To send you information about Services that may be of interest to you based on your preferences
* To prevent and detect fraud, or enforce our legal rights

**3. SHARING INFORMATION  
**

We do not sell or trade personal information. The Company may share your personal information with third parties, such as Services operators or technicians, contracted to assist us in providing services to you or to effectuate any of the purposes set forth in the list above. This means that individuals and organizations outside of the Company may sometimes have access to personal information held by the Company and may collect or use it from or on behalf of the Company. This may include, but is not limited to, independent contractors and consultants, website hosts, electronic database managers, event managers, academic institutions, research institutions and our researcher partners.

Such third party service providers are precluded in their contracts with the Company from keeping or using your personal information for any purpose other than to provide assistance to us in relation to the Services.

We may also disclose personal information to professional advisors of the Company, such as accountants, lawyers or insurance brokers or underwriters.

We also may disclose and/or transfer personal information to a third party in the event of a proposed purchase, sale, merger, financing, restructuring or similar type of transaction involving the Company. We reserve the right to disclose and/or transfer personal information to a third party if required by law or pursuant to a court order or subpoena, or if necessary in the Company’s reasonable opinion to identify someone in order to enforce the Company’s legal rights.

Please note that this Policy is not intended to limit our ability to use, retain or disclose aggregated, pseudonymized, or anonymized data.

**4\. REMOVING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We will endeavor to honor a request to delete your personal information. If for whatever reason you wish to remove personal information obtained by the Company, we will endeavor to remove your personal information. If you would like your personal information deleted, please contact us at Info@constructivedialogue.org.

**5\. RETENTION OF INFORMATION**

We will keep your personal information for the period of time that you are a registered user on the Services, and for TEN (10) years after you cancel your registration or cease use of the Services.

**6\. SECURITY**

The security and protection of your personal information is important to us. The Company endeavors to use reasonable security procedures and practices to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure or destruction of your personal information. However, internet communications or transmissions are not totally secure, and you transmit your personal information to us at your own risk. The Company does not and cannot warrant total security. Our Services may contain links to websites of independent third parties, and in such events your use of such websites is at your own risk, and you should review their respective terms and conditions and privacy policies (including their terms governing security) prior to use.

**7\. CHILDREN**

We do not target our Services to children under 13 and do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete it in accordance with applicable law.

**8\. USE OF COOKIES.**

A cookie is a small electronic file placed in your web browser by a website when you visit that website. It is designed to help manage that website’s use. Cookies can also store certain preference information to help customize your website experience. We use cookies to help us understand how consumers use our Services so we can design better services in the future. Web browsers can be adjusted to disable cookies. However, the Company may not be able to provide you with all the functionality you desire on the Services if you choose to disable them. You may also remove cookies from your browser. Please refer to your browser’s help menu for instructions. If you need assistance from the Company, please contact us at info@constructivedialogue.org

\[The Company confirms that it will respect “do not track” signals from customer browser settings.\]

****9\. QUESTIONS****

If you have questions about our Services or this Privacy Policy, please contact the Company’s Legal Department by email at info@constructivedialogue.org, or by mail at 244 Madison Avenue #1098, New York, NY 10016. You may make an anonymous communication in relation to our Services or this Privacy Policy, but we may require you to identify yourself if that is required by law or if it is reasonably necessary in order to deal with your matter otherwise. We will endeavor to respond to you in a timely manner.

**10\. **MODIFICATIONS****

The Company reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify at any time this Privacy Policy or any portions thereof. In the event of any such modification(s), the Company will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Services, and setting out the effective date. Those modifications will go into effect on the effective date stated. By continuing to use this Services or any of the Services after the effective date, you accept unconditionally and agree to all such changes in the revised Privacy Policy or provisions. If you do not agree to such changes, you must discontinue use of the Services as your sole remedy.

Privacy Notice

This site uses cookies. Please click accept to continue, or visit our [Privacy Policy](https://constructivedialogue.org/privacy) to learn more.

AcceptClose

### 

Curiosity. **Critical Thinking.** Compassion.

[](https://openmindplatform.org/)© 2024 Constructive Dialogue Institute[Privacy Policy](https://openmindplatform.org/privacy/)[Terms of Service](https://openmindplatform.org/terms-of-service/)[990s](https://openmindplatform.org/990s/)

* Other Sectors

The Constructive Dialogue Institute is a 501(c)3 nonprofit organization. Donate today to support our work

Close
